job4u.ae 2018-08-22

# Jobs in UAE - Privacy Policy | job4u.ae

## PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICIES

We recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all products and services provided by us.

### PRIVACY POLICY

#### Collection of Information

We collect various information when you register with JOB4U.AE, during your usage of our services, when you visit pages of our partners. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from other partners or other companies in order to provide you a better experience or to improve the quality of our services. When you sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. We automatically receive and record information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, our cookie information, software and hardware attributes the page you request and other standard browser parameters. 

We collect the following personal information: 

From Candidates

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, phone number
  * Profession-related information such as profession, experience, education etc.

From Companies

  * Contact Information such as company name, email address, phone number, contact person
  * Company profile.

From all our customers

  * Unique Identifiers such as primary email, password
  * Usage activity about how you interact with us such as purchase history, what content you viewed, and which areas of our site you visited.

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. 

#### We use this information to

  * Provide our services
  * Fulfill your order
  * Send tax invoice and service voucher
  * Send personal job offers from registered user
  * Alert about new vacancies for your profession
  * Send ad response to the advertisers
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Respond to your questions and concerns

#### Opt Out / Mail delivery control

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by click on unsubscribe link included to all our emails. 

You can control all our mail delivering to you via the Control Panel in your Cabinet. 

#### Disclosure to Third Party

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. 

We may disclose your personal information: 

  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so
  * We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users by demographic. Such information does not identify you individually.

#### Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

#### No Spam Policy

We have a strict No-Spam Policy prohibiting the use of any data collected to send spam. We will not sell any contact information to third parties. 

#### Accessing and Updating Personal Information

We provide our customers with full control over their personal information on our website including update or even complete removal all their information from our system. 

PLEASE NOTE: all information regarding financial activities of our clients can not be removed from our system as it should be kept for at least 5 years as per UAE law. 

### COOKIES POLICY

When you use our services, we send one or more cookies - text-only pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual/’s hard drive or other website-browsing equipment for record-keeping purposes. All our cookies are encrypted and don't contain personal information like your name or email. 

We use cookies to: 

  * Provide our services
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services
  * Remember user's choice and preferences to provide him with better experience
  * Track user's activities on our website
  * Avoid misuse of our system

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case we may not be able to provide those services to you. 

### PRIVACY DISCLAIMER

All credit/debit cards’ details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties. 

SIP FZ LLE will not pass any debit/credit card details to third parties. 

SIP FZ LLE takes appropriate steps to ensure data privacy and security including through various hardware and software methodologies. However, JOB4U.AE cannot guarantee the security of any information that is disclosed online. 

SIP FZ LLE is not responsible for the privacy policies of websites to which it links. If you provide any information to such third parties different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply. You should contact these entities directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. 

### CHANGES OF THIS PRIVACY / COOKIES POLICY

JOB4U.AE Policies and Terms & Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. Therefore, the Customers are encouraged to frequently visit these sections to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted.
